{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20known%20as%20the%20'King%20of%20Pop'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Michael%20Jackson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elvis%20Presley",
        "Stevie%20Wonder",
        "Prince"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20composer%20is%20famous%20for%20the%20'Fifth%20Symphony'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ludwig%20van%20Beethoven",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Wolfgang%20Amadeus%20Mozart",
        "Johann%20Sebastian%20Bach",
        "Franz%20Schubert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20considered%20the%20'Father%20of%20the%20Symphony'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Joseph%20Haydn",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Wolfgang%20Amadeus%20Mozart",
        "Ludwig%20van%20Beethoven",
        "Johann%20Sebastian%20Bach"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20composer%20is%20known%20for%20the%20opera%20'The%20Magic%20Flute'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Wolfgang%20Amadeus%20Mozart",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ludwig%20van%20Beethoven",
        "Johann%20Sebastian%20Bach",
        "Franz%20Schubert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20known%20as%20the%20'King%20of%20Blues'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "B.B.%20King",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elvis%20Presley",
        "Stevie%20Wonder",
        "Chuck%20Berry"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20composer%20is%20known%20for%20the%20piece%20'Clair%20de%20Lune'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Claude%20Debussy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Johann%20Sebastian%20Bach",
        "Ludwig%20van%20Beethoven",
        "Wolfgang%20Amadeus%20Mozart"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20musician%20is%20known%20as%20the%20'Guitar%20God'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jimi%20Hendrix",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Eric%20Clapton",
        "Jimmy%20Page",
        "Carlos%20Santana"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20composed%20the%20'Bolero'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Maurice%20Ravel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Claude%20Debussy",
        "Georges%20Bizet",
        "Erik%20Satie"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20composer%20is%20known%20for%20the%20opera%20'Carmen'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Georges%20Bizet",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jacques%20Offenbach",
        "Giacomo%20Puccini",
        "Giuseppe%20Verdi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20known%20as%20the%20'Father%20of%20the%20Blues'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "W.C.%20Handy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scott%20Joplin",
        "Bessie%20Smith",
        "Ma%20Rainey"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
